DANIEL LE

Address: Fitzroy, Melbourne VIC 3065, Tel: 0421 470 854

Email: LinkedIn: Portfolio:

ltpd175@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/hiiammeo/ https://hiiammeo.github.io/

Career Profile

Master's in Data Science candidate, experience in agile project management and an excellent work ethic. Project experience in AI and knowledge of Object-Oriented Analysis and Design, combined with experience working flexibly at different technical positions. Learning new languages and technologies is what I am passionate about. I am considered a team-player because I like to help other and tend to work well within the group. I can also do some mentoring tasks and do code reviews for other team members.

Technical Skills

- Programming Languages:
 - C#.NET. Python, Javascript, Java,
 - HTM5, CSS3
- Frameworks/Platforms:
 - NodeJS, ASP.NET, Jupiter Notebook
 - Android Studio, Google API, Linux
- Data Analysis Tools:
 - RStudio, Tableau, Power BI
- Others:
 - Good understanding of OOP Methods Experience with Agile and Scrum development process
 - Intermediate Design, Photoshop and Video Editing

Employment History

January 2024 – Present: IT Support Officer

AUG Student Service, Melbourne

- Tech-savvy & Solutions-Driven: From AI videos to websites and CRM data. resolving IT issues, optimising processes, and collaborating effectively to enhance team success.
- AUGTrix & Web Dev Specialist: Proficient in system enhancement and data management. Delivery of impactful results that contribute to Augtrix's continuous improvement.

Version Control System:

C++, Ruby and Rails

Database/Management Systems:MySQL, CRM System

Github

Foundation:

 Dedicated and Passionate: Committed to excellence, with valuable insights and proactive assistance to ensure seamless alignment with organizational goals.

October 2023 – Jan 2024: IT Intern Programmer

August 2022 - October 2022: Intern Programmer

AI Internship, Strong Compute Corporation, Remote

- Organised review existing benchmark results for 5 popular models and datasets.
- Accomplished training dataset skills from working flexibly with 4 datasets and other technologies.
- Collaborated smoothly within a team of 4 people under minimal supervision.

Relevant Experience

Dec 2022 – Mar 2024: Front & Back of House Staff - Miss Saigon Chadstone, Melbourne, VIC

Achievement: Collaboration, Time Management, Teamwork, Communication

Jul 2021 - Oct 2022: Head Chef - Le Feu GF Restaurant Company, Melbourne, VIC

Achievement: Leadership, Organization, Professionalism, Management

Projects

March 2022 - October 2022: Full Stack Developer

Voice Verification - Ontrack Deakin, Group project

- Created a voice verification system, aiming to increase 30% the ability of universities to address cheating activities in online learning.
- Gained experience working as a full-stack developer by utilizing 5 different front-end applications and relative libraries for back-end applications.
- Built communications among a team of 7 people and external stakeholders.

March 2022 - June 2022: Created self

Investigating Reinforcement Learning, Individual project

- Created self-directed study into 3 advanced aspects of reinforcement learning (Cart-Pole/Mountain/Taxi problem).
- Provided solutions to real-world problems of an AI agent through interaction with its environments and multiple feedback signals.
- Received High Distinction.

Education

March 2024 – Presents: Master of Data Science

March 2020 - November 2022: Bachelor of Computer Science

Completed with Distinction

March 2020 - October 2020: Diploma of Information Technology

• Completed with High Distinction

Referees

• Cian Byrne.

• Lai Hy

- Internship Supervisor.
- System Business & Data Analytics Manager
- cian@strongcompute.com.
- laihy@augstudy.com